粘合带放大20倍成像荷兰金箔残留成分
是的
That is correct.
而且除了金箔外没有别的东西了
And there was nothing else.
-没有灯或地毯上的铅化合物吗  -没有
- No lead from the lamp or the rug? - No.
就是说写着阿瓦尔卡女士名字的便利贴
Meaning Ms. Abarca's note
是从夏加尔的画上掉落的
had to fall from the Chagall painting?
-是的  -你应该说反对
- That's correct. -You should object.
反对  法官阁下
Objection, Your Honor.
无相关性
Relevance?
猜得很用心  但错了
Good guess. No.
法官阁下
Your Honor,
我方认为夏加尔的画是留给
we believe that the Chagall painting
斯马尔德斯夫人的管家  塞利娜·阿瓦尔卡的
was left to Mrs. Smulders' housekeeper, Selina Abarca,
我方请求裁定
and we ask that Your Honor rule.
辩方有什么要补充的吗
Does Counselor have anything?
我方申请诉讼延期  法官阁下
Again we ask for a continuance, Your Honor.
洛克哈特女士的论据很有说服力
Ms. Lockhart has made a very strong argument.